Zachary Dunham

web developer

About Me

Web developer with 3 years of professional experience. Proven work with dozens of clients to ensure their sites were not only running smoothly, but looking great as well. Passionate about both front-end and back-end development and a love to learn.

Details

Portfolio https://zdunham.dev/

Email me@zdunham.dev

Location Buffalo, NY

Phone (716) 270-3657

Skills

Languages

TypeScript/JavaScript PHP SOL

HTML/CSS C#

Technologies

C/C++

Git Magento 2 React/Next.js Docker Linux

Education

Rochester Institute of Technology (2016 - 2022) Bachelor of Science in Game Design and Development

Experience

Web Developer | Computer SOS, Inc.

November, 2021 - Present | Buffalo, NY / Remote

- Set up and maintained sites using the Magento ecommerce platform
- Developed numerous custom modules for clients using Magento
- Helped to maintain and update proprietary software to facilitate synchronizing data between NCR Counterpoint and Magento
- Helped to manage projects, onboard new clients, and train new developers
- Developed scripts to make the onboarding and training process easier

Web Developer | Changeling VR

June, 2020 - August, 2020 | Rochester, NY / Remote

- Worked with a team of students to create a website to host a virtual reality game
- Tasked with creating two webpages, as well as helping more inexperienced team members develop their pages further

Projects

Cardle

https://cardle.wtf/

- Daily game where users guess a Pokémon card from a blurred image
- ❖ Gets card data from an API, stores locally within a MongoDB database
- Stores data for previous days for an archive
- Built using React/Next.js and Tailwind

RCON Web GUI

https://github.com/zsd7200/rcon

- Allows connection to game servers using the RCON protocol
- Stores data for server information within an SQLite database
- Designed to be self-hosted via Docker
- Built using React/Next.js and Tailwind

BonesNode

https://bonesga.me/

- Port of the dice game "Dice 10,000" (also known as "Bones") to web using Node.is
- Uses Socket.io to create rooms to be able to connect and play with other people
- Includes a chat feature to talk with other players in your private room